cloudprohosting.com 2016-06-27

# Privacy Policy - Cloud Based Web Hosting by Cloud Pro Hosting - 99.9% Uptime Web Hosting

## 1\. Introduction

Welcome to the Cloud Pro Hosting website, a company registered in and governed by the laws of the United States. 

Protecting your privacy is a serious matter and doing so is very important to cloudprohosting.com (also hereinafter referred to as "Cloud Pro Hosting", "we", "us" or "our"). No personal information will be shared with any third parties without the customer"s permission. Please read this Privacy Policy statement (the "Policy") to learn more about our Policy.

This Policy applies to information collected on the Cloud Pro Hosting web site, applications and services (the "Service") and covers our treatment of personally identifiable information/data ("Personal Information") and other data that we gather when you are accessing our Service.

We reserve the right to modify our Policy at any time and without prior notice, so be sure to check this Policy regularly to understand how we use your information. If you do not accept and agree with our Policy then you may not access or use the Service.

## 2\. Personal Information You Provide to Cloud Pro Hosting

We receive and store any information you enter on our Service or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected may include your name, address, email address, phone number, location, usage information regarding your use of our Service, and browser information.

The Personal Information you provide is used for such purposes as allowing you to set up a user account and subscribe to the Service, improving the content of the Service, customizing the content you see, and communicating with you about updates, offers and new features. We may also draw upon this Personal Information in order to adapt the Service to your needs, to research the effectiveness of our Service, and to develop new tools.

## 3\. Information Collected Automatically by Cloud Pro Hosting

When you use the Service, Cloud Pro Hosting automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser or mobile platform, including your location, IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. We treat this data as non-personal information, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. Cloud Pro Hosting only uses this data in aggregate form.

## Log Files

Like most standard websites, Cloud Pro Hosting uses log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer our website, track user's movement in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. However, none of the information stored in the Cloud Pro Hosting log files, including but not limited to IP addresses, is linked to Personal Information.

## Clear Gifs

We may use third party advertising partners that employ a software technology called Clear Gifs (also known as Web Beacons or Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our website by indicating to us which content is effective. Clear Gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. Unlike cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, Clear Gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages. We do not tie the information gathered by Clear Gifs to any Personal Information.

## 4\. Subscription Information

When you subscribe to the Service, we collect financial information necessary to process your payments in accordance with the payment method chosen by you. Please note that we or our payment service providers store payment details (and are approved to do so by all regulatory bodies).

## 5\. How We Use Personal Information

Information about our customers is an integral part of our Service. We use the Personal Information you submit to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionalities of the Service. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We may share your Personal Information only as described herein.

We use the information we collect (including your Personal Information) to create a better, more personalised experience for you based on your individual usage habits, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, analyse usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our Service. This improves our Service and allows us to better customize it to meet your needs. We may also use the information we collect about you to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and to enforce our Terms of Service.

By providing us with your email address, you consent to our using the email address to send you Service-related notices, including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. We may also use your email address or phone number to send you other messages, such as newsletters, changes to features of the Service, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such messages, you may opt out or change your preferences in your profile settings page. Opting out may prevent you from receiving messages regarding updates, improvements, or offers. You may not opt out of Service-related e-mails. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the ownership rights over the content of any your email messages to us and our responses sent to you.

## 6\. How Information is Shared

## Information shared with other Users and the Public

Any Personal Information or content that you voluntarily disclose or upload to public areas (on our website) while using the Service becomes available to the public. Cloud Pro Hosting shall not be responsible for the Personal Information that you choose to disclose publicly on the Service. Should you remove information that you posted to the Service copies may remain viewable (i) in cached and archived pages of the Service, or (ii) if others have copied or saved that information. Individuals reading this information may use it or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge. We therefore urge you to think/consider carefully prior to posting any specific information you may deem private in content that you create in the Service. 

## Information shared with Partners and Affiliates

We may provide information in aggregate form to our partners and affiliates about how our users, collectively, use our Service, so that they may also understand how often people use their services and our Service. We may use for promotional/sales purposes or for any other purposes that we consider appropriate your correspondence with us or content submitted by you for publication on our Service, whether it be via email, postings on our website and mobile device software applications, or via feedback (for instance members/users" polls). Our use of such materials/contents/information/data is compliant with the restrictions on disclosure of Personal Information set forth herein. 

## Information shared with Agents

We employ/hire other companies and/or individuals ("Agents") to perform tasks on our behalf and we need to share your information with them to provide the Service to you. Our agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us, and they provide a comparable level of protection for your Personal Information. 

## Required disclosures

We may need to disclose your Personal Information when required by law or if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us, (b) enforce this Policy and/or our Terms of Service, (c) respond to claims that your Personal Information violates the rights of third parties; or (d) protect the rights, property or personal safety of Cloud Pro Hosting, its users/customers and the public. You hereby authorize us to disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to any kind of liability. 

## Business Transfers

If Cloud Pro Hosting or substantially all of its assets are acquired by any third party, all of our customers/user's information (including any Personal Information) would be one of the assets that is transferred to or acquired by such a purchasing third party. 

## 7\. Reviewing, Updating, Deleting and Deactivating Personal Information

Following your subscription to our Service, we provide you with a way to update your Personal Information. Subject to our Terms of Service, you may terminate/close your account at any time. Once your account is terminated, we have the right to delete any content that you have submitted or uploaded to the Service. Upon our receipt of your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate your account and remove your Personal Information as soon as reasonably possible in accordance with our Terms of Service and with any applicable law.

Nonetheless, we will retain in our files information you may have requested us to remove if, in our discretion, retention of the information is necessary to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems or to enforce our Terms of Service. Furthermore, your information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints (for example, we will not remove your information from our back up storage). 

## 8\. How We Protect Personal Information

Cloud Pro Hosting uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Cloud Pro Hosting and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive any such of information from you, Cloud Pro Hosting makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that we do not guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

To protect the privacy and security of your information, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique identification information, and for controlling access to your communications from Cloud Pro Hosting, at all times. 

## 9\. Compromise of Personal Information

In the event that any Personal Information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will promptly notify those persons whose Personal Information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Policy, or as otherwise required by any applicable law. 

## 10\. Dispute Resolution

Any dispute, claim or controversy arising out of or in connection with this Policy or previous privacy policy statements shall be resolved through negotiation, mediation and litigation as provided under our Terms of Service. 

## 11\. Contact Information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this Policy, please contact our Customer Support team by email at support@cloudprohosting.com 

## 12\. Effective Date

This Policy was last updated on 26 July 2012. It is governed by the Terms of Service.
